A Guide to the Overseas Development Council records FA788
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Overseas Development Council Photographs, 1972-2000; 14; 4.52 Cubic Feet 11 letter document boxes, 1 half-letter document box and 1 photo box
  - International Summit on Economic Restructuring and Social Policy, 1995 January (Box 61, Folder 744)
  - Social Summit, 1995 March (Box 61, Folder 745)
  - Speth Dinner, 1995 June 1 (Box 61, Folder 746)
  - Labor Conference, 1995 October 12 (Box 61, Folder 747)
  - Shalala/Somavia Luncheon, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 748)
  - Jacque De Lerosiere, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 749)
  - JWS, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 750)
  - ODC/ICRW Meeting, 1995 July 21 (Box 61, Folder 751)
  - CSF, 1994 March 10 (Box 61, Folder 752)
  - Washington Exchange, 1994 April (Box 61, Folder 753)
  - PEB, 1994 May 3 (Box 61, Folder 754)
  - Joan Nelson and her contributors, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 755)
  - 4th Annual Convocation, 1993 October 13-14 (Box 61, Folder 756)
  - Michel Camdessus CSF, 1993 February 16 (Box 62, Folder 757)
  - Gronkiewicz-Waltz CSF, 1993 September 24 (Box 62, Folder 758)
  - CSF, 1993 June 11 (Box 62, Folder 759)
  - Congressional Staff Forum, 1993 May 24 (Box 62, Folder 760)
  - Manmohan Singh Lunch, 1993 September 23 (Box 62, Folder 761)
  - Ernie Wilson Hill Seminar, 1993 March 19 (Box 62, Folder 762)
  - Atwood CSF, 1993 July 21 (Box 62, Folder 763)
  - Japan Conference, 1993 May 10-11 (Box 62, Folder 764)
  - Bd Retreat, 1992 April (Box 62, Folder 765)
  - Premise and Promise Conference, 1992 July 27 (Box 62, Folder 766)
  - Maurice Strong, 1992 January 8 (Box 62, Folder 767)
  - Board Meeting, 1992 November 19 (Box 62, Folder 768)
  - Olesegun Obasanjo, 1992 (Box 62, Folder 769)
  - Babacar Ndiaye Dinner, 1992 March 18 (Box 62, Folder 770)
  - Congressional Staff Luncheon, 1992 (Box 62, Folder 771)
  - JICA Lunch, 1991 November 22 (Box 62, Folder 772)
  - Environment and Trade Conference, 1991 February 11 (Box 62, Folder 773)
  - Congressional Staff Forum, 1991 Fall (Box 62, Folder 774)
  - Gus Speth Lunch, 1994 June 1 (Box 62, Folder 775)
  - 3rd Annual Convocation, 1991 June 24-25 (Box 62, Folder 776)
  - Annual Meeting, 1990 November 15 (Box 62, Folder 777)
  - Iracle Conference, 1990 October 15 (Box 62, Folder 778)
  - African Development Bank, 1990 March 26 (Box 62, Folder 779)
  - Jimmy Carter, 1990 July 23 (Box 62, Folder 780)
  - Mexico Free Trade Agreement Conference, 1990 October 25 (Box 62, Folder 781)
  - Jim Grant, 1990 December (Box 62, Folder 782)
  - Grants Dinner with Solomon, 1990 February 22 (Box 62, Folder 783)
  - Congressional Staff Forum, 1990 December (Box 62, Folder 784)
  - Poverty and Environment Breakfast Series, 1989 (Box 62, Folder 785)
  - Porter Dinner, 1989 October 18 (Box 62, Folder 786)
  - Lee Hamilton, 1989 (Box 62, Folder 787)
  - Bukman, 1989 April 3 (Box 62, Folder 788)
  - Dinner and Breakfast Meetings, 1989 December (Box 62, Folder 789)
  - Idriss Jazairy at CSF, 1989 (Box 62, Folder 790)
  - IMF Conference, 1989 September 14 (Box 63, Folder 791)
  - Annual Meeting, 1989 November 6-7 (Box 63, Folder 792, Folder 793)
  - Annual Meeting, 1988 (Box 63, Folder 794)
  - Annual Meeting, 1987 December 2 (Box 63, Folder 795)
  - African Development Bank Dinner, 1987 February 17 (Box 63, Folder 796)
  - Jim Grant Dinner, 1987 (Box 63, Folder 797)
  - Babbitt Dinner, 1987 (Box 63, Folder 798)
  - Board Meeting with Yuetter Lunch, 1987 (Box 63, Folder 799)
  - Chairman's Breakfast Series, 1987 (Box 63, Folder 800)
  - Congressional Staff Forum, 1988 (Box 63, Folder 801)
  - Iglesias Dinner, 1988 June (Box 63, Folder 802)
  - Agenda Conference, 1988 (Box 63, Folder 803)
  - Does Aid Work?, 1986 December 9 (Box 63, Folder 804)
  - Whitehead Reception, 1986 October 7 (Box 63, Folder 805)
  - Investment Conference, 1986 May 28 (Box 63, Folder 806)
  - Annual Council Meeting, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 807)
  - ODC Receptions, 1986 December 4 (Box 64, Folder 808)
  - Southern African Conference, 1986 September 25-26 (Box 64, Folder 809)
  - World Bank Conference, 1986 June (Box 64, Folder 810)
  - Grant Dinner, 1985 December 4 (Box 64, Folder 811)
  - Council Meeting, 1985 November 13 (Box 64, Folder 812)
  - African Press Briefing, 1985 December 2 (Box 64, Folder 813)
  - John Gavin Dinner, 1985 May 8 (Box 64, Folder 814)
  - Africa, 1984 November 29 (Box 64, Folder 815)
  - Annual Meeting, 1984 (Box 64, Folder 816)
  - Trade Conference, 1984 September 28-29 (Box 64, Folder 817)
  - Board Meeting, 1983 November 16 (Box 64, Folder 818)
  - Trop Dis, 1982 March 4 (Box 64, Folder 819)
  - Board Meeting, 1982 May 20 (Box 64, Folder 820)
  - Banker/Grant, 1982 January 28 (Box 64, Folder 821)
  - Fujioka, 1982 September 21 (Box 64, Folder 822)
  - Hesburgh/McNamara Press Lunch, 1982 January 20 (Box 64, Folder 823)
  - Agenda '82 Press Lunch, 1982 February 25 (Box 64, Folder 824)
  - Board Meeting, 1982 February 4 (Box 64, Folder 825)
  - Mexico, 1982 April 18 (Box 64, Folder 826)
  - Cancun Press Briefing, 1981 October 9 (Box 64, Folder 827)
  - Recap/Board Meeting, 1981 October (Box 64, Folder 828)
  - Rashish Dinner, 1981 September 17 (Box 64, Folder 829)
  - Population, 1981 July 14 (Box 64, Folder 830)
  - Franklin Thomas/Sen. Kassebaum, 1981 July 8 (Box 64, Folder 831)
  - Feintech Dinner, 1981 August 19 (Box 64, Folder 832)
  - Cesar Virata, 1981 September 23 (Box 64, Folder 833)
  - Horst Schulmann, 1981 September 30 (Box 64, Folder 834)
  - Board Meeting, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 835)
  - Global 2000, 1980 October 14 (Box 64, Folder 836)
  - Capital Access to Developing Countries, 1980 July 22 (Box 64, Folder 837)
  - N-S Energy Dinner, 1980 July 17 (Box 64, Folder 838)
  - Pol Risk Dinner, 1980 September 9 (Box 64, Folder 839)
  - Agenda Release, 1980 September 9 (Box 64, Folder 840)
  - Zimbabwe Dinner, 1980 June 24 (Box 64, Folder 841)
  - Cambodia, 1979 October 24 (Box 64, Folder 842)
  - Overseas Mission, 1977 April 27 (Box 64, Folder 843)
  - 1979, 1979 October 16 (Box 65, Folder 844)
  - Sarbanes/Whalen Dinner, 1978 March 21 (Box 65, Folder 845)
  - Juan Somavia Dinner, 1978 February 9 (Box 65, Folder 846)
  - Iqbal Akhund Dinner, 1978 March 7 (Box 65, Folder 847)
  - Jawara Dinner, 1978 May 25 (Box 65, Folder 848)
  - Board Meeting, October 1977 (Box 65, Folder 849)
  - Agenda Press Conference, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 850)
  - Board Meeting, 1976 October (Box 65, Folder 851)
  - Mead/Tinker Press Conference, 1976 (Box 65, Folder 852)
  - Financing Problems for the Developing World, 1976 May 12 (Box 65, Folder 853)
  - Agenda Press Conference, 1977 (Box 65, Folder 854)
  - Krishna Moorthi Dinner, 1977 May 26 (Box 65, Folder 855)
  - Hiller Tourism, 1974 January 30 (Box 65, Folder 856)
  - Dialogue in World Development, 1974 March 18-21 (Box 65, Folder 857)
  - Theodore Hesburgh, 1971 October 15 (Box 65, Folder 858)
  - Misc. Photos, 1974 (Box 65, Folder 859)
  - HAQ Luncheon, 1974 (Box 65, Folder 860)
  - Migration Dinner, 1974 (Box 65, Folder 861)
  - Human Rights Dinner, 1974 (Box 65, Folder 862)
  - Miscellaneous, 1978-1980 (Box 65, Folder 863)
  - Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 864)
  - Archive Pictures - Undated (Box 65, Folder 865)
  - Miscellaneous - Undated (Box 65, Folder 866)
  - Miscellaneous - Undated (Box 65, Folder 867)
  - Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 868)
  - Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 66, Folder 869)
  - Board Meeting, 1972 October (Box 66, Folder 870)
  - Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 66, Folder 871)
  - Miscellaneous - Undated (Box 66, Folder 872)
  - Miscellaneous - Undated (Box 66, Folder 873)
  - 3rd Convocation, 1991 June 24-25 (Box 66, Folder 874)
  - Annual Meeting + Misc., 1989 (Box 66, Folder 875)
  - Annual Meeting + Misc., 1989 (Box 67, Folder 876)
  - Annual Meeting, 1989 (Box 67, Folder 877)
  - Annual Meeting, 1989 (Box 67, Folder 878)
  - World Bank Conference, 1986 June (Box 67, Folder 879-880)
  - Unidentified Photos, 1995-1999 (Box 68, Folder 881-882)
  - Miscellaneous, 1995-1999 (Box 69, Folder 883)